Long Island society gasped...but this Texas buckaroo landed in romance!
The Kid From Texas is a comedy, romance, western
film directed by S. Sylvan Simon.
A loud-mouthed Texas cowpuncher tries his hand at polo finding himself at odds
with high society and trying to save a floundering Wild West show.
William Quincy, played by Dennis O'Keefe.
Margo Thomas, played by Florence Rice.
Bertie Thomas, played by John Hubbard.
Aunt Minetta, played by Jessie Ralph.
'Snifty', played by Buddy Ebsen.
'Okay' Kinney, played by Virginia Dale.
The Kid from Texas is a 1939 Western sports comedy film.
The film explores themes of texas, fish out of water, wild west show, polo.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.